[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "For the removal of which of these waste products is blood responsible?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Lactic acid", "Carbon dioxide", "Urea"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The largest commonly available domino set is the Double Twelve consisting of 91 tiles.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of pasta is used for the making of the popular Spanish dish Fideua?", "correct_answer": "Vermicelli", "incorrect_answers": ["Sheet noodles", "Rice noodles", "Spaghetti"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "There actually was a pink submarine in WWII, like the one featured in the movie Operation Petticoat.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What were the first names of the brothers who directed the documentary about Grey Gardens?", "correct_answer": "Albert and David", "incorrect_answers": ["Alfred and David", "Albert and John", "David and John"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What are the names of the two people who practice shooting in a scene of the film Babel?", "correct_answer": "Yuseff and Mohammed", "incorrect_answers": ["Santiago and  Jorge", "Julio and Ramon", "Rinko and  Yasujiro"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This author wrote a book in which the story is told from the view poin of the mulatto slave Cynara, born on the plantation Tata.  The book is a parody of  the novel Gone with the Wind.", "correct_answer": "Alice Randall", "incorrect_answers": ["Maya Angelu", "Toni Morrisson", "Valerie Drew Pierce"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What happens to a goldfish when it is kept in the dark?", "correct_answer": "It turns a paler color.", "incorrect_answers": ["It turns white.", "It goes blind.", "It dies."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What German car make, founded in 1931, is famous for its high performance luxury automobiles?", "correct_answer": "Porsche", "incorrect_answers": ["Volkswagen", "Mercedes-Benz", "BMW"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which countrys capital city is considered de facto capital of the European Union?", "correct_answer": "Belgiums", "incorrect_answers": ["UKs", "Hollands", "Frances"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "From what famous movie is the quote Im the king of the world!?", "correct_answer": "Titanic", "incorrect_answers": ["Rocky", "Raging Bull", "Jerry Maguire"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This was the first country that starts with the letter J to join the United Nations.", "correct_answer": "Jordan", "incorrect_answers": ["Jurasconia", "Jamaica", "Japan"]}]